const programming=[
{
	question:"What are the types of linkages?",
	options:['Internal and External','External, Internal and None','External and None'],
	answer:'External, Internal and None'
},
{
	question:"By default a real number is treated as a",
	options:['float','double','long double'],
	answer:'double'
},
{
	question:") Which is a reserved word in the Java programming language?",
	options:['method','subclasses','native'],
	answer:'native'
},
{
	question:"When we mention the prototype of a function?",
	options:['Defining','Prototyping','Declaring'],
	answer:'Declaring'
},
{
	question:"Which is a valid keyword in java?",
	options:['interface','string','Unsigned'],
	answer:'interface'
},
{
	question:"A pointer to a block of memory is effectively same as an array",
	options:['True','False','undetermined'],
	answer:'True'
},
{
	question:"Which is a reserved word in the Java programming language?",
	options:['method','native','array'],
	answer:'native'
},
{
	question:"What is the numerical range of a char?",
	options:['-128 to 127','0 to 32767','0 to 65535'],
	answer:'0 to 65535'
},
{
	question:"What is the name of the method used to start a thread execution?",
	options:['init();','start();','run();'],
	answer:'start();'
},
{
	question:"Which is valid declaration of a float?",
	options:['float f = 1F;','float f = 1.0;','float f = "1";'],
	answer:'float f = 1F;'
}
]